<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml> <correspondent sex="Male"><name>Salsette Frigate</name></correspondent>, <date datetime= "1810-05-03">3 May 1810</date> <letterBody>****This morning I swam from Sestos to Abydos. The immediate
    distance is not above a mile, but the current renders it hazardous; – so much so that I doubt
    whether Leander’s conjugal affection must not have been a little chilled in his passage to
    Paradise. I attempted it a week ago, and failed, – owing to the north wind, and the wonderful
    rapidity of the tide, – <byronSkill skill="Swim">though I have been from my childhood a strong swimmer</byronSkill>. But, this morning
    being calmer, I succeeded and crossed the <location location="Narrow passage in the Aegean Sea">‘broad Hellespont’</location> in an hour and ten minutes. Well,
    my dear sir, I have left my home, and seen part of Africa and Asia, and a tolerable portion of
    Europe. I have been with generals and admirals, princes and pashas, governors and ungovernables,
    – but I have not time or paper to <vocabulary definition= "To talk or write in detail">expatiate</vocabulary>…. I like the Greeks, who are plausible rascals, –
    with all the Turkish vices, without their courage. However, some are brave, and all are
    beautiful, very much resembling the busts of <vocabulary definition ="A flamboyant Athenian statesman">Alcibiades</vocabulary>; – the women not quite so handsome. I
    can swear in Turkish; but, except one horrible oath, and ‘pimp’ and ‘bread’, and ‘water’, I have
    got no great vocabulary in that language. They are extremely polite to strangers of any rank,
    properly protected**** I am like the <vocabulary definition= "A once traditional folk song in Northern England">Jolly Miller</vocabulary>, caring for nobody, and not cared for. All
    countries are much the same in my eyes. I smoke, and stare at mountains, and twirl my mustachios
    very independently. I miss no comforts, and the mosquitoes that rack the morbid frame of H.
    have, luckily for me, little effect on mine, because I live more temperately.**** My paper is
    full, and my ink ebbing – good afternoon! If you address to me at Malta, the letter will be
    forwarded wherever I may be. H. greets you; he pines for his poetry, – at least, some tidings of
    it. I almost forgot to tell you that I am dying for love of three Greek girls at Athens,
    sisters, I lived in the same house. Teresa, Mariana, and Katinka, are the names of these
    divinities, – all of them under fifteen. Your ‘<vocabulary defintion= "NULL">Tapeinotatos doulou</vocabulary>s’, BYRON <context>Byron wrote the
    lyric ‘On Swimming from Sestos to Abydos’ about this experience</context>.</letterBody> </xml>
